welcome to voiceprint identification
when you see the red light go on with
your free state in the following order
your destination your nationality and
your full name
boom american flight they would on
thank you you are cleared through
voiceprint identification
frankly we have had some reliable
intelligence reports that quite a
serious epidemic programmatically well
there have been some hectic views held
by some of you regarding the need for
security
however I accept the need for absolute
secrecy discussed
we thought it might be the upper part of
some very structure so we excavated out
on all sides but unfortunately we didn't
find anything else and hasn't been
covered up by natural erosion or other
forces seems to have been deliberately
very
more 15 year old black monolith remain
completely enter her fingers
very well written within three weeks ago
the American spacecraft discovery one
that applies half-eaten mile voyage to
the sixth member of the discovery rule
is the HAL 9000 computer
everything is going extremely well one
gets the sense that he is capable of
emotional responses pile of dead
no 9000 computer has ever made a mistake
or distorted information that they have
I can't put my finger on Center Street
yesterday , mr. , you know what happened
and sorry Dave
I don't have enough to get ready to help
with your lady are we straight there
now they are you reading
you're reading out do you read me out
this machine is too important for me to
learn your improvising
I don't know what you're talking about
this conversation and serve no purpose
anymore
yeah